aquaveo.com 2019-04-23

# AQUAVEO PRIVACY POLICY | Aquaveo.com

Aquaveo respects the privacy of all individuals who visit [www.aquaveo.com](http://www.aquaveo.com/) and/or purchase our products or services. This Privacy Policy is our commitment to transparency in communicating how Aquaveo collects, uses, and discloses the information that is collected from you.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**Evaluations/Events/Marketing Participants** \- Individuals that evaluate our software or participate in events, surveys, contests, and/or those who subscribe to marketing material do so voluntarily and may be asked for the following information:

  * name
  * business name
  * email address
  * physical address
  * phone number
  * fax number

You may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this personal data.

**Website Visitors** \- At your option, Aquaveo asks and may collect the following when using certain features of our website:

  * name
  * business name
  * email address
  * physical address
  * phone number

In addition, we also collect information such as web server logs, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, or other information as part of aggregated data.

**Customers** \- Aquaveo asks for your account information which includes the following:

  * Name
  * Business name
  * Email address
  * Physical address
  * Phone number
  * Fax number
  * Credit card information (temporarily stored with a third party processor)

By voluntarily providing Aquaveo with your account information, you represent that you own and consent to our use of such personal data.

### COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

Aquaveo uses cookies, tags, and other tracking technologies on our website to gather information about you, identify your visits, and customize your experience. This information is stored in log files and may include:

  * Internet protocol (IP) addresses
  * Internet service provider (ISP)
  * Operating system
  * Browser type
  * Date/time

You can control how our website uses cookies by changing your browser settings. This may limit your use and functionality of some features on our website.

### SSL ENCRYPTION

[www.aquaveo.com](http://www.aquaveo.com/) uses SSL encryption for security and to protect the transmission of sensitive content, such as the requests you send to us. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line displaying "https:" and a lock symbol. If SSL encryption is enabled, the data you submit to us cannot be read by third parties.

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

Aquaveo uses the information collected in the following ways:

  * To respond to any requests from you regarding sales and support
  * To contact you regarding any agreements or accept any terms that you may have with Aquaveo for products or services
  * To contact you regarding functionality changes to our products, services, or website
  * To collect payment and bill for our products or services
  * To help personalize experiences on our website
  * To diagnose problems
  * To find and prevent fraud
  * To carry out other purposes as disclosed to you through the website, or found in terms or an agreement between you and Aquaveo

### HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

Aquaveo shares the information it collects about you in the following ways: 

  * **Third Party Developers** \- Aquaveo may share your information with third party developers that have granted Aquaveo a right to distribute their software in our products. The information is provided to these companies or individuals in order to document software purchases and to provide technical support to end users.
  * **Advertising** \- Based on the cookies and other tracking devices, we may work with advertising companies to display ads that may be of interest to you.
  * **Business Transactions** \- To provide information to a third party in the event of any disposition of all or any portion of our business (e.g. reorganization, sale, assignment, bankruptcy).
  * **As Required by Law or Similar Investigations** \- To comply with legal obligations (e.g. subpoena) or investigate potential legal violations. Aquaveo may be required to share personal data in response to lawful requests from public authorities including to meet national security and/or law enforcement requirements
  * **Safety** \- We may disclose your information to protect and defend the safety of Aquaveo in connection with investigating and preventing fraud or security issues.
  * **Consent** \- Aquaveo may share your information with your consent

### YOUR CHOICES

You may unsubscribe from receiving promotional or marketing emails from Aquaveo at any time by using the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email received, or by emailing us at [support@aquaveo.com](mailto:support@aquaveo.com). As outlined in the section, Cookies and other Tracking Technologies, you can also control your cookie settings.

With respect to your account information, you may update, correct, or delete information that you provided to us by contacting us at [support@aquaveo.com](mailto:support@aquaveo.com).

### CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

Aquaveo reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time.

### CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns over this Privacy Policy, or wish to update, correct, or delete your information, please contact us at:

**Aquaveo, LLC**  
Attn: Support  
3210 N. Canyon Road, Suite 300  
Provo, UT 84604  
United States  
Email – [support@aquaveo.com](mailto:support@aquaveo.com)
